ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
Orchid.
Lord Changheng!
Lord Changheng, where are you?
Lord Changheng--
Didn't I tell you to run
as far away as possible?
Why are you back here?
Let go of me! Lord Changheng is in danger.
I have to find him.
You're in my body now.
I'm afraid
that before you can talk to him,
you would be killed by his sword.
Let's switch back first.
What will happen after we switch back?
Will you take the opportunity
to kill Lord Changheng?
Even if he hurt me by mistake,
I won't give you
the opportunity to do that.
Orchid.
Orchid!
- Orchid! Where are you?
- Lord--
- Shut up.
- Lord Changheng!
- Orchid!
- Stay here.
- Let go.
Fine, go.
He'll kill you as soon as he sees you.
Then he'll take me back
to Shuiyuntian as you.
As long as I can get close to him
and stay by his side,
I can kill him sooner or later.
Orchid!
Orchid.
- You…
- Hide.
Promise me you won't hurt him.
Hurry up.
If you break your promise,
I'll kill myself
and you'll be trapped in my body forever.
Orchid, I finally found you.
Let's go.
I'll take you back.
Orchid, don't be afraid.
I'm here to take you back.
I believe you are not a spy.
Lord Changheng trusts me.
He even came to Cangyan Sea to save me.
But I'm not worthy.
Why is he so kind?
My lord, please leave.
I'm already used to living
in Cangyan Sea's Silent Moon Palace.
I don't want to leave.
What…
What do you mean?
Orchid.
Is someone threatening you?
Don't be afraid. Tell me.
I'll protect you.
No one is threatening or forcing me.
It's my own choice.
Since I came to Cangyan Sea,
I've been eating well and living well.
The doctors used the best medicine
to heal my whip wounds.
I'm also not what you consider
a lowly spirit,
a traitor, or a spy
who colluded with the Moon Tribe.
I can be myself happily.
Compared to the days
when everyone in Shuiyuntian can bully me,
it's over 100 times better.
Don't speak nonsense.
That's not what I'm thinking.
Orchid,
you're just mad, aren't you?
That day at Yunzhong Water Pavilion,
my brother only hurt you
due to a misunderstanding.
If I go back with you,
are you sure you can clear my name
about colluding with the Moon Tribe?
- I--
- If Lord Yunzhong refuses to pardon me,
do you dare disobey him?
If he uses heavenly orders and rules
to question you and force you,
can you protect me?
If anyone dares to hurt me or blame me,
will you make their soul dissipate?
My brother has always been impartial.
I believe
he will find out the truth.
I knew you couldn't do it.
You wouldn't even tell me
words of comfort.
But the Moon Supreme Lord
can do all of this.
He is willing to protect me
and not let anyone hurt me.
That's why I'm willing to stay here.
Did you just call him
the Moon Supreme Lord?
Are you really colluding
with the Moon Tribe?
That's impossible.
You're Shuiyuntian's fairy.
No matter what happens,
I must take you back to Shuiyuntian.
Let's go.
I said I'm not leaving.
Orchid.
- Who is it?
- Stop.
Ronghao? Why are you…
How can I feel at ease
when you sneak out of Shuiyuntian alone?
Hurry!
Hurry up and surrender!
- Hurry!
- Don't kill me!
I'll…
You…
Are you really Orchid?
I finally found you.
I knew you weren't a spy.
Don't be afraid.
I'll break the spell for you.
Wait.
I'm afraid even you can't break it.
Even if there is a way to break it,
you can't do it.
Because…
Because this way, Dongfang Qingcang
will also regain his power.
She's right.
If Dongfang Qingcang regains his power,
based on our powers,
we won't be able to escape.
What should we do then?
You risked your life to save me.
I'm already very grateful.
I dare not drag you down.
Why don't you take this opportunity
to leave?
No.
I have an idea.
If we extract your spirit
and bring it back to Shuiyuntian,
we can use the Self-Renewing Soil
to create a new body
and turn you back into Orchid safely.
Good idea.
This way,
we can seal Dongfang Qingcang
in Fairy Orchid's old body.
As long as we destroy this body,
Dongfang Qingcang will die.
And he will be gone from this world.
- No.
- No!
No.
They switched back.
You promised me you wouldn't hurt him.
You are injured.
I have an unfair advantage.
Get lost.
Lord Changheng!
What are you doing?
- I…
- Don't follow me!
My lord.
Lord Xunfeng broke into the palace
at night with an army
and started a mutiny.
Due to its urgency,
I acted on my own and mobilized
the Dayu and Tieyu Forces.
They've surrounded Silent Moon Palace.
Now, upon your order,
we'll attack
and take back Silent Moon Palace.
There's no need.
I can do it alone.
My lord,
I couldn't find you just now.
What happened?
Xunfeng,
how dare you sit on my throne?
Stop pretending.
Dongfang Qingcang?
SHUYU FOREST, SHUIYUNTIAN
Changheng.
Hang in there.
We're almost there.
My lord,
you've locked yourself
in the room all day.
You haven't taken the elixir yet.
You used a lot of power to repair
the Four-River Pearl before.
You have to nourish yourself.
My lord.
I'm coming in then.
FOUNTAIN PALACE
- My lord.
- Changheng is sick.
- Aren't you in--
- Go and get medicine.
Danyin?
Lord Ronghao,
I'm begging you.
You must save Changheng.
Are there any Immortal Pills left?
No.
If there are
no Immortal Pills left,
how about Guangfu Pill?
My father has a lot of medicine.
I'll go and get some now.
Wait.
Do you want everyone in Shuiyuntian
to know that Changheng disobeyed orders
and went to Cangyan Sea?
Then what should we do?
When he repaired the Four-River Pearl,
his vitality was damaged.
This time at Cangyan Sea,
he was attacked with evil qi
and was hurt by Dongfang Qingcang,
causing his Immortal Pond to disappear.
To save him,
we can only use the life-prolonging
cultivation transfer method.
I'm willing to transfer
my cultivation to him.
You don't have enough cultivation.
If we want to cultivate Changheng,
we need a higher level of cultivation.
But I heard that the cultivation transfer
method damages one's cultivation badly.
My lord, you…
It has been tens of thousands of years.
I drank so many good wines from Changheng.
Consider this as my compensation.
It's the evil qi again.
My lord, I've investigated.
Lord Xunfeng
secretly colluded with Haishi.
This mutiny
was their conspiracy.
They wanted to assassinate you
and take the Moon Supreme position.
I'm not surprised
that Xunfeng wants to kill me.
But why does the Lord of Haishi
want to kill me?
Does he covet Cangyan Sea too?
Since he can control evil qi,
he can use it to control Xunfeng
and the Kings of North and South You.
If he just wanted to be the leader
of the Moon Tribe,
he could have replaced me
before I came back.
He's secretly keeping Lady Chidi's
primordial spirit and Destiny Book
while helping Xunfeng
to fight against you.
What exactly does he want?
Keep an eye on Xunfeng.
I'll interrogate him myself.
Yes.
Shangque.
When did you know I was weak
and had no power?
I knew it since the first day.
When she pretended to be you,
she told me her power was damaged.
But I didn't know
about the body switch then.
When I saw it with my own eyes yesterday,
I finally understood everything.
Why didn't you kill me?
The one who kills me
can be Moon Supreme.
Why would I kill you?
You are the most important person to me.
You are like a brother to me.
I would never betray you.
I don't think so.
I think Shangque
is quite affectionate to you.
He will never betray you.
What do you know?
I just know.
You don't understand the heart
and emotions.
That's why you don't know.
You may go.
I'll get going.
My lord.
In order to save Changheng,
you lost half of your cultivation.
Your hair turned gray.
I want to turn you back
into your previous self.
Even if you use up all your cultivation,
it won't work.
Don't be silly.
I understand.
But for your sake, I have no regrets.
You don't have to do this.
You don't have
to prolong Changheng's life either.
I know.
You're not a heartless person.
You risked your life to save Changheng
because you've known him for 30,000 years.
The same goes for me.
- Enough!
- That's why--
I saved Changheng
because I still need him.
I need him to fight against Cangyan Sea
and destroy Dongfang Qingcang.
That's all.
What happened in Silent Moon Palace?
Xunfeng was defeated
and captured by Dongfang Qingcang.
He's locked up in Wind Prison.
My lord.
Should we send someone to kill him?
There's no need.
Dongfang Qingcang is very cruel.
He even killed his biological father.
Why would he care about Xunfeng?
Yes.
Orchid.
Orchid!
Lord Changheng.
You're awake?
Don't move.
You haven't recovered yet.
My lord, where are you going?
Danyin,
bring me my armor.
No.
Are you going to Cangyan Sea again?
I already blamed myself
for helping you before.
Do you know
how badly injured you are now?
In order to save you,
Lord Ronghao used half of his cultivation.
Can you…
Ronghao?
He…
You haven't recovered yet.
Where are you going?
If you don't care about yourself,
I care about my power.
I've made up my mind.
When I come back,
I'll bring you the best wine in the world.
FOUNTAIN PALACE
Lord Yunzhong
summoned you to Yunzhong
Water Pavilion for questioning.
Changheng.
You secretly went to Cangyan Sea.
Do you admit your mistake?
You did it
just for the Moon Tribe's spy
who hid Dongfang Qingcang?
She's not a spy.
You're wise, Lord Yunzhong.
Dongfang Qingcang lurked in Shuiyuntian
and even saved that unknown spy.
He must be up to something.
Changheng sneaked into Cangyan Sea alone
to catch the spy
and figure out Dongfang Qingcang's plan.
Although this is reckless,
he was just eager to kill the enemy.
Yes.
Lord Changheng cares
about the safety of Shuiyuntian.
Switching bodies
was my idea.
Punish me if you want.
Changheng.
Answer me.
Like Ronghao said,
I was…
just eager to kill the enemy.
I was reckless.
I've sealed your power temporarily.
Go back to Fountain Palace
to reflect on your mistake.
Remember.
Don't repeat your mistake.
Orchid.
You finally got a chance
to go back to Shuiyuntian,
but you didn't grab it.
Look at what happened.
Your crime of colluding
with the Moon Tribe is completely proven.
Lord Changheng
must be very disappointed in you.
He won't come to save you again.
He will never trust you again.
I let Lord Changheng down.
Orchid,
you're thinking too much.
You are just an unknown lowly spirit.
Now, you're even labeled as a traitor.
Lord Changheng is the God of War.
He came to save you
out of responsibility and kindness.
Why would he protect you so much?
Could it be…
Am I…
That's impossible.
He's the Moon Supreme Dongfang Qingcang,
Shuiyuntian's greatest enemy.
Anyway, I just want to tell you
that the person I like is Lord Changheng,
not you!
I also hope that Lord Changheng
is the one by my side,
not you.
Do you understand?
The person I want to see
is Lord Changheng.
The real Lord Changheng,
not the one you're pretending to be.
You promised me you wouldn't hurt him.
My lord.
How is she?
I observed her the whole afternoon.
After Fairy Orchid went back,
she was quite well-behaved.
She either walked under the tree
or sighed.
Nothing special.
I see. You may leave.
Yes.
Wait.
What did you call her?
"Fairy Orchid"?
When did you start respecting
this little flower spirit?
My lord, you're not aware.
Although no one knew
about the body switch between you and her,
the palace maids are secretly saying
that when Lord Xunfeng
broke into the palace yesterday,
she was the one who came forward
and saved you.
In order to thank her for saving you,
they all call her Fairy Orchid in private.
I'm also used to calling her that
and forgot the difference
between the two tribes.
It seems like she has become
Silent Moon Palace's distinguished guest.
Exactly.
To thank her,
the palace maids want
to arrange a banquet for her.
But I don't know if you'll allow it.
After all, you personally grounded her.
The people dare not disobey it.
She's no longer grounded then.
By the way,
not only is she no longer grounded…
Pass on my message.
From now on, she can move freely
in Silent Moon Palace
and Cangyan Sea.
No one can stop her
or be rude to her.
And no one can hurt her.
Otherwise, they'll be killed.
Aren't you afraid that she will run away?
She has openly helped me
in front of Changheng.
It's no different
from betraying Shuiyuntian.
Other than Cangyan Sea,
where else can she go?
My lord, you're really intelligent.
Fairy Orchid has always wanted to escape.
But she gave up
such a good opportunity yesterday
to save you.
It shows that…
What?
It shows that she's submitting willingly.
She has become
a loyal subordinate like me
who would die for you.
What do you know?
I'm stupid.
Please enlighten me.
If what she did
wasn't loyalty, then what was it?
Since you came back,
Silent Moon Palace is finally lively.
Would you like to attend the banquet too?
It's a good sign for the unity
of the Moon Tribe
and the revival of Cangyan Sea.
That's ridiculous.
It's a gathering of women.
It's inappropriate for me to go.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
- Fairy Orchid!
- Come here.
- Look.
- You're so pretty.
- It's pretty.
- Yes. You're gorgeous.
- It's beautiful.
- This is nice.
- This is really something else.
So beautiful.
You look so elegant.
- Let's…
- Right.
This is too pretty.
It's so rare.
- That's great.
- I envy you.
Try this on.
- Let me see it.
- Try this.
I didn't expect Cangyan Sea's
most fashionable outfit
to look so beautiful on you.
If a stranger sees this,
they'd think she's from the Moon Tribe.
Who would think
that she's a fairy from Shuiyuntian?
It's so beautiful!
It's so pretty!
It's so nice!
- Come on, let's circle around together.
- It's so beautiful!
- It's so pretty.
- It's so beautiful.